Duel 1v1 Updated

An updated version of Duel 1v1 with a new map, balance changes for a more fair fight and to prevent trolling, and bug fixes.

Each player starts at level 25 with infinite gold. You have 60 seconds to buy items, then the first round starts. When a player dies, cooldowns and buffs reset (including those such as legion commander's duel damage bonus), and you have 30 seconds to adjust your item build, then a new round starts. The first player to reach 5 kills wins.

Players can start the round early if all players click the "Ready up" button.

If a player disconnects or does not pick a hero, they will lose.

To make the gamemode more balanced and a more accurate simulation of the lategame in a normal DOTA 2 match, the following changes have been made:

- Rapier is banned
- Black king bar is always at lowest duration and cooldown
- Bloodstone cannot be used to commit suicide, and does not lose or gain charges when you die or kill an enemy

Also, both players can pick the same hero.

If you have feedback or found a bug, please leave a comment or open a discussion on the workshop page, or open an issue on Github:
https://github.com/pengowen123/dota_duel1v1_updated



0 Bloodstone
1 Does not have charges. Instead grants 12 Mana Regeneration.

8 Disabled
9 Disabled until the round starts. Use this time to buy or change your items.

10 Outside the arena
11 You will be killed in 8 seconds unless you enter the arena.

13 Gives Pudge 12% additional resistance to spells

19 Gives Pudge resistance to magic damage. Does not grant bonus strength.

21 awarding victory to
22 A player did not pick a hero
23 A player has disconnected
24 Starting next round in: 60 seconds
25 Ready up